http://www.probikekit.com/site-info/privacy-policy.list

Introduction
Probikekit is committed to protecting our customer's privacy. Please
take the time to review this notice which explains what information we
collect about you, how we use it, and your rights. The Hut.com Limited
(“Probikekit”, “we” or “us”) is the data controller of the personal data
collected via or in connection with www.probikekit.co.uk and any
associated App (the “Site”).
What personal data do we collect about you?
We collect personal data from you when you provide it to us directly
and through your use of the Site. This information may include:-
Information you provide to us when you use our Site (e.g. your name,
contact details, gender, product reviews, and any information which you
add to your account profile);- Transaction and billing
information, if you make any purchases from us or using our Site (e.g.
credit/debit card details and delivery information);- Records of your interactions with us (e.g. if you contact our customer service team, interact with us on social media)- Information you provide us when you enter a competition or participate in a survey;-
Information collected automatically, using cookies and other tracking
technologies (e.g. which pages you viewed and whether you clicked on a
link in one of our email updates).
We may also collect information
about the device you use to access our Site; and- Other information necessary to provide the Site, for example we may access your location if you give us your consent.If
you also shop in one of our stores, we may combine information you give
us in-store (e.g. if you make a purchase or join our mailing list
in-store) with the information above.
What do we use this personal data for?
Depending on how you use our Site, your interactions with us, and the
permissions you give us, the purposes for which we use your personal
data include:- To fulfil your order and maintain your online account.- To manage and respond to any queries or complaints to our customer service team.-
To personalise the Site to you and show you content we think you will
be most interested in, based on your account information, your purchase
history and your browsing activity.- To improve and maintain the Site, and monitor its usage.- For market research, e.g. we may contact you for feedback about our products.-
To send you marketing messages and show you targeted advertising, where
we have your consent or are otherwise permitted to do so.- For
security purposes, to investigate fraud and where necessary to protect
ourselves and third parties. To comply with our legal and regulatory
obligations.We rely on the following legal basis, under data protection law, to process your personal data:-
Because the processing is necessary to perform a contract with you, or
take steps prior to entering into a contract with you (e.g. where you
have made a purchase with us, we use your personal data to process the
payment and fulfill your order).- Because we have obtained your
consent (e.g. where you contact us with a query, where you add optional
information to your account profile, or if you consent to receive
marketing from us).- Because it is in our legitimate interests
as an e-commerce provider to maintain and promote our services. We are
always seeking to understand more about our customers in order to offer
the best products and customer experience. We use information about you
to tailor your view of the Site, to make it more interesting and
relevant in respect of the products and offers on view.Our
Site may allow you the option of adding additional information to your
account profile, such as information about your body type, skin type,
hair type, hair condition, training regime, performance goals, height
and weight. We treat this information with particular sensitivity, as we
understand it can reveal information about your health or ethnicity,
for example. You do not have to provide this information to us, and can
delete it or update it at any time.
Marketing
We love to communicate with our customers and so, depending on your
marketing preferences, we may use your personal data to send you
marketing messages by email, phone or post. Some of these messages may
be tailored to you, based on your previous browsing or purchase
activity, and other information we hold about you.If you no
longer want to receive marketing communications from us (or would like
to opt back in!), you can change your preferences at any time by
contacting us (details below), clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any
email, or updating your settings in your account. If you unsubscribe
from marketing, please note we may still contact you with service
messages from time to time (e.g. order and delivery confirmations, and
information about your legal rights).You may also see ads for our
Site on third party websites, including on social media. These ads may
be tailored to you using cookies (which track your web activity, so
enable us to serve ads to customers who have visited our Site). Where
you see an ad on social media, this may because we have engaged the
social network to show ads to our customers, or users who match the
demographic profile of our customers. In some cases, this may involve
sharing your email address with the social network. If you no longer
want to see tailored ads you can change your cookie and privacy settings
on your browser and these third party websites.
Who do we share this personal data with?
We share customers’ personal data with third parties in the following circumstances:With other companies in our group of companies, as necessary to operate the Site.With our suppliers and service providers working for us, e.g. payment processors and delivery companies.With our professional and legal advisors.With third parties engaged in fraud prevention and detection.With law enforcement or other governmental authorities, e.g. to report a fraud or in response to a lawful request. In the event that we sell any business assets, the personal data of our
customers may be disclosed to a potential buyer. In this event, we will
make reasonable attempts to ensure the buyer will be bound by the terms
of this Privacy Policy.Otherwise where we have your consent or are otherwise legally permitted to do so.
Storage & Retention
We use service providers based around the world. Consequently, your
personal data may be processed in countries outside of Europe, including
in countries where you may have fewer legal rights in respect of your
data than you do under local law. If we transfer personal data outside
the European Economic Area we will, as required by applicable law,
ensure that your privacy rights are adequately protected by appropriate
safeguards, in particular the EU’s standard contractual clauses. Please
contact us if you would like more information about these safeguards.We
will keep your personal data for as long as we need it for the purposes
set out above, and so this period will vary depending on your
interactions with us. For example, where you have made a purchase with
us, we will keep a record of your purchase for the period necessary for
invoicing, tax and warranty purposes. We may also keep a record of
correspondence with you (for example if you have made a complaint about a
product) for as long as is necessary to protect us from a legal claim.
Where we no longer have a need to keep your information, we will delete
it. Please note that where you unsubscribe from our marketing
communications, we will keep a record of your email address to ensure we
do not send you marketing emails in future.
Security
This Site ensures that data is encrypted
when leaving the Site. This process involves the converting of
information or data into a code to prevent unauthorised access. This
Site follows this process and employs secure methods to ensure the
protection of all credit and debit card transactions. Encryption methods
such as SSL are utilised to protect customer data when in transit to
and from this Site over a secure communications channel. Whilst we doeverything
within our power to ensure that personal data is protected at all times
from our Site, we cannot guarantee the security and integrity of the
information that has been transmitted to our Site.
Children
Our Site is not intended for, and should not be used by, children under
the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children
under 18.
Cookies
Our Sites uses cookies and similar technologies to provide certain
functionality to the Site, to understand and measure its performance,
and to deliver targeted advertising. Please see our Cookie Policy here for further information about the cookies we use and how to amend your cookie settings.
Your Rights
You have certain rights in respect of your personal data, including
the right to access, portability, correct, and request the erasure of
your personal data.You also have the right to object to your personal data being used for certain purposes, including to send you marketing. See ‘Marketing’ above, for more details of how to opt-out of marketing.We
will comply with any requests to exercise your rights in accordance
with applicable law. Please be aware, however, that there are a number
of limitations to these rights, and there may be circumstances where we
are not able to comply with your request. To make any requests regarding
your personal data, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding
your personal data, you should contact us using the details below. You
are also entitled to contact your local supervisory authority for data
protection.
Contact Us
If you have any queries on any aspect of our Privacy Policy, please contact us on the details below:Telephone: 0161 8131481Email: customer.experience@thehutgroup.comAddress: Customer Services, Meridian House, Gadbrook Park, Cheshire, CW9 7RA
Last updated
16th May 2018
